<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>tEp</title>
    <link>http://tep.mit.edu/</link>
    <description>Recent content on tEp</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 25 Aug 2016 01:09:54 -0400</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://tep.mit.edu/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>The Gospel According to Nick Hanssens</title>
      <link>http://tep.mit.edu/the-gospel/the-gospel-according-to-nick-hanssens/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Aug 2016 01:09:54 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://tep.mit.edu/the-gospel/the-gospel-according-to-nick-hanssens/</guid>
      <description>&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I look back and I cannot help but think about how much I learned while living at tep. Yes, I learned to cook and to handle money and to fix things; but, at least for me, that isn&amp;rsquo;t what was important. There were the times when trying to relate to 30 people felt overwhelming and pointless; and there were the times the house was there for me when I really needed it to be.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I learned how to trust a compatriate only because he knew what you were going through. I learned how somebody you don&amp;rsquo;t like can save you. I learned how an awkward &amp;lsquo;I don&amp;rsquo;t know what to say&amp;rsquo; or a fumbled hug can make all the differance in the world. I learned how to talk to people about things that I really thought I couldn&amp;rsquo;t. I learned that trying to reach out or trying to listen, even if you fail, can honestly help. I learned that I can help those around me whom I love when they need it. I learned that love isn&amp;rsquo;t a sexual thing.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;MIT is a difficult place, and the value of having people around you who know what you are going through is immense. I am a better person for having gone through tep, and I notice the same differences in trust and confidence every day across my colleagues who joined fraternities and those who didn&amp;rsquo;t.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;— Nicholas &amp;ldquo;Qwidgibo&amp;rdquo; Hanssens &amp;lsquo;01&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Gospel According to Wally Holland</title>
      <link>http://tep.mit.edu/the-gospel/the-gospel-according-to-wally-holland/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Aug 2016 01:09:54 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://tep.mit.edu/the-gospel/the-gospel-according-to-wally-holland/</guid>
      <description>&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;quarter of two a.m.. two hours ago, pounding down the street, will and rhett at my heels, the only thought to get to the ice cream shoppe before it closes. wet ground, the occasional car. boston still alive at that time of night, but headed for bed shortly. on the stereo, u2. &amp;ldquo;still haven&amp;rsquo;t found what i&amp;rsquo;m looking for&amp;rdquo;. not exactly true, is it? something special here. got cookies and cream, size medium, and colyn insisted that we go to the supermarket afterward, silly thing really, only we&amp;rsquo;d go any damned place at that time of night, if you asked.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;across the hall, bo doing that weird thing with his mouth while he studies, some freshman class. he does the same thing when he plays the bass, that chipmunk-cheeked expression. like there&amp;rsquo;s a smile about to burst out. we all get together and play at cocoa sometimes: twenty-two dollar budget for snacks, and a steaming cauldron of cocoa (except the nights someone makes goddamn lemonade, but i guess i shouldn&amp;rsquo;t complain). invite everyone we know over, and this strange assortment of people sort of spills all over our living room. like someone upended a box of weirdos. nice to see so many boys, girls, people from all over the institute. usually a good audience, as well, couldn&amp;rsquo;t tell you why. guess it takes that spark to see what&amp;rsquo;s special about this place. just left-of-center, where it belongs.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;i miss edgar. not that we take the fraternity practice of &amp;ldquo;big brother/little brother&amp;rdquo; that seriously, mind you: he still owes me that dinner, because a box of mcnuggets isn&amp;rsquo;t going to cover it. i remember last year, the first time i did rush from the other side of the line, how difficult it was. one day just broke down in tears (lots of reasons, i guess, but you know what 19-year-olds are like). he walked by, and didn&amp;rsquo;t say anything, just lay down and hugged me. stayed that way for a while: you need the release of it, sometimes, the tears. afterward we laughed at it all, at how love is love, and little enough to be sad about. was making straight a&amp;rsquo;s in eight classes when he left to join the army. wonder how he&amp;rsquo;s doing?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;something told me it was a little different here, even that first meeting when i arrived at mit. i was ready for water war, for kiddie pools of oobleck, for the hanging couch, the foam room, the lemon pie performance art. i wasn&amp;rsquo;t ready for seppo crying when he moved out, for friday nights with rota and half the house, for eric&amp;rsquo;s marriage at the aquarium, for the fred event, for the five of us sleeping in a basement in chicago, for holding nick&amp;rsquo;s hand when i was sad.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;been wondering lately about a lot of things, same as always: mit doesn&amp;rsquo;t let you off easy. don&amp;rsquo;t know about computer science, or graduate school, or midterms. i know i&amp;rsquo;m someplace unique, though. &amp;ldquo;don&amp;rsquo;t dream it&amp;rsquo;s over&amp;rdquo; plays, a kind of lullaby for a rainy night. feel so completely safe, so at home here. so difficult to just explain why: people ask, i always end up with, &amp;ldquo;you&amp;rsquo;ve just got to be there. to live it for a while.&amp;rdquo; sounds like a cop-out, but how else can i explain? i heard a man say to me, &amp;ldquo;i love my brothers,&amp;rdquo; and as silly as it sounds, i know he meant it: because i feel the same way. every once in a while, things just work. something about these guys: they just work.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;— Walter &amp;ldquo;Minwax&amp;rdquo; Holland &amp;lsquo;01&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Iron tEps: Insect Edition</title>
      <link>http://tep.mit.edu/rush/sept07/ironteps/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Sep 2015 18:22:00 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://tep.mit.edu/rush/sept07/ironteps/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Tired of steak and lobster? Come bake and eat some land invertebrates instead.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dim Sum</title>
      <link>http://tep.mit.edu/rush/sept07/dimsum/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Sep 2015 12:22:22 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://tep.mit.edu/rush/sept07/dimsum/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;I&amp;rsquo;m sure you&amp;rsquo;ve all heard of Riemann sums, direct sums, wedge sums, free products,
and disjoint unions, but have you heard of DIM sum?? Meet at tEp for a lazy Monday afternoon dim sum.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>More oobleck!</title>
      <link>http://tep.mit.edu/rush/sept05/more-oobleck/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 05 Sep 2015 21:22:00 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://tep.mit.edu/rush/sept05/more-oobleck/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;The oobleck&amp;rsquo;s getting cooler, but the kiddie pool&amp;rsquo;s getting hotter!&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Oobleck</title>
      <link>http://tep.mit.edu/rush/sept05/oobleck/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 05 Sep 2015 20:22:00 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://tep.mit.edu/rush/sept05/oobleck/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;1000 pounds of non-Newtonian fun. Towels and spare clothes provided.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>LN2 Spice Cream</title>
      <link>http://tep.mit.edu/rush/sept05/spice-cream/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 05 Sep 2015 19:22:00 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://tep.mit.edu/rush/sept05/spice-cream/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Spice Cream: Final Showdown. Which spice is best in ice cream? Will it be returning champion &lt;code&gt;Capsaicin&lt;/code&gt; or the new challengers &lt;code&gt;Piperin&lt;/code&gt; or &lt;code&gt;Cinamalehyde&lt;/code&gt;?&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Duck Duck Chili</title>
      <link>http://tep.mit.edu/rush/sept05/duckduckchili/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 05 Sep 2015 18:22:00 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://tep.mit.edu/rush/sept05/duckduckchili/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Join us on our waddling quest to discover the best Thai food in Boston.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bleached T-Shirt Design</title>
      <link>http://tep.mit.edu/rush/sept05/bleached-t-shirt/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 05 Sep 2015 15:22:22 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://tep.mit.edu/rush/sept05/bleached-t-shirt/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Make your own stenciled and bleach-washed shirt. Caution: Oxidizers &lt;em&gt;(but I&amp;hellip;)&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ganzfelding &#43; Science Smorgasbord</title>
      <link>http://tep.mit.edu/rush/sept05/ganzfelding/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 05 Sep 2015 14:22:22 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://tep.mit.edu/rush/sept05/ganzfelding/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;What do butterflies and 3D printed lattices have in common? Find out! &lt;em&gt;Speaking of radiation&amp;hellip;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Japanese Griller</title>
      <link>http://tep.mit.edu/rush/sept05/japanesegriller/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 05 Sep 2015 12:22:00 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://tep.mit.edu/rush/sept05/japanesegriller/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Make your own sushi and eat it too!&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>http://tep.mit.edu/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://tep.mit.edu/</guid>
      <description>
&lt;figure &gt;
    
        &lt;img src=&#34;img/home.jpg&#34; /&gt;
    
    
&lt;/figure&gt;


&lt;p&gt;One of the most unique and mature aspects of MIT is the diverse range of living opportunities available to fit our student body. You have experienced but the tip of the iceberg until you taste of the great wild world that lies just ex loco parentis.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Tired of the blandness of the dorms? Want something different? tEp is a unique place where you can find a whole new level of independence from the &amp;lsquo;tvte.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The rules we follow at tEp are the rules we choose for ourselves. It&amp;rsquo;s a lot of responsibility to govern yourself, but hell, you&amp;rsquo;re an adult, and we&amp;rsquo;re sure you can handle it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;tEp is an amazing place filled with some of the most inventive and creative people at MIT, and is a place where standard operating procedure is to be working on 22 projects at a time, all of them totally rockin&amp;rsquo;. It&amp;rsquo;s a great, creative, and fun environment where nothing seems impossible, and the founding of your own company, or the discovery of a new planet, seem equally within your reach. Our info page has some of the neat things that have happened because of tEps in the recent past.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Drop by tEp and you might not want to leave. Meat the brothers, have a grape söder, crash in the Free Willy net, and forget about whatever you should&amp;rsquo;ve already forgo&amp;hellip;. tEp is many things to many people, but for all who live here it&amp;rsquo;s our home — as well as a covert operations center, culinary &amp;ldquo;research&amp;rdquo; lab, artistic studio, and philosophical playground. It&amp;rsquo;s not right for everyone — nothing is. Some, though, find a family where they can thrive and grow as never before.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Contact Info</title>
      <link>http://tep.mit.edu/contact/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://tep.mit.edu/contact/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Phone Number:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;code&gt;617.262.5090&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Do you need a ride? Call us at the above number, and we&amp;rsquo;ll pick you up in our van.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Address:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;code&gt;253 Commonwealth Avenue Boston, MA 02116&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&#34;iframe-wrp&#34;&gt;
&lt;iframe src=&#34;https://www.google.com/maps/embed?pb=!1m28!1m12!1m3!1d5896.898689460932!2d-71.09279773708866!3d42.35426215709833!2m3!1f0!2f0!3f0!3m2!1i1024!2i768!4f13.1!4m13!3e2!4m5!1s0x89e370a99a9f9fdf%3A0x949c51dad93fec80!2s77+Massachusetts+Ave%2C+Cambridge%2C+MA+02139!3m2!1d42.3592539!2d-71.0931342!4m5!1s0x89e37a0f3c3d6b9d%3A0xfb5e9f810e870fdd!2s253+Commonwealth+Avenue%2C+Boston%2C+MA!3m2!1d42.350918!2d-71.083522!5e0!3m2!1sen!2sus!4v1441483949819&#34; width=&#34;600&#34; height=&#34;450&#34; frameborder=&#34;0&#34; style=&#34;border:0&#34; allowfullscreen&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Directions&lt;/strong&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;From MIT&lt;/strong&gt;: Walk 22 minutes from MIT, or take the Saferide Boston East to the first stop (Mass Ave and Beacon St) and walk from there.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Elsewhere&lt;/strong&gt;: You&amp;rsquo;re on your own.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Email&lt;/strong&gt;: (get on our mailing list)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&#34;iframe-wrp&#34;&gt;
&lt;iframe src=&#34;https://docs.google.com/forms/d/e/1FAIpQLSeTe5GGEle-KjO76p-634j0P1RvtW4wOe4r3txyctp_Nvfmyw/viewform?embedded=true&#34; 
    width=&#34;100&#34; height=&#34;1000&#34; frameborder=&#34;0&#34; marginheight=&#34;0&#34; marginwidth=&#34;0&#34;&gt;Loading...&lt;/iframe&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tour</title>
      <link>http://tep.mit.edu/tour/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://tep.mit.edu/tour/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;You&amp;rsquo;ve heard stories about tEp: a.k.a. the purple palace, the last stronghold of the knights of the lambda calculus, the U.S.S. Birthday Ship. You&amp;rsquo;ve been meaning to get over there to see what it&amp;rsquo;s all about.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;But, you are lazy. Instead, you went to the tEp website and opted for the &lt;em&gt;virtual&lt;/em&gt; house tour. We understand.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This site brings you to such a virtual house tour. It is a multimedia text adventure game. But, while you can interact with the tour conventionally using the keyboard,
&lt;strong&gt;you can also click on the links and the purple map&lt;/strong&gt;, which will automatically type the corresponding command for you.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For your tour, we are providing you with Irving Q. Tep, the spirit of the house. He&amp;rsquo;ll be giving you the descriptions and stories you will read during your tour.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Without further ado:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;http://tep.mit.edu:8888/game/teptour&#34;&gt;I want to go on the tour!&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>